[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Robert Redford, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Robert", "Redford", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "Well, so far, so good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "so", "far", ",", "so", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Redford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "EDFORD: Oh, you like that?", "question_tokens": ["EDFORD", ":", "Oh", ",", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, I made her do that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "made", "her", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Do you get hundreds, thousands, possibly in your case, millions of people telling you how they've changed their lives because you've had their lives altered?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "hundreds", ",", "thousands", ",", "possibly", "in", "your", "case", ",", "millions", "of", "people", "telling", "you", "how", "they", "'ve", "changed", "their", "lives", "because", "you", "'ve", "had", "their", "lives", "altered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "That's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Even with \"All the President's Men\"?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "with", "``", "All", "the", "President", "'s", "Men", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "``", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, I'm wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "You think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "I guess OK with your wife, huh?", "question_tokens": ["I", "guess", "OK", "with", "your", "wife", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "And I think it worked out pretty well.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "it", "worked", "out", "pretty", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "I heard that you don't watch your own movies?", "question_tokens": ["I", "heard", "that", "you", "do", "n't", "watch", "your", "own", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, not all of them, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "all", "of", "them", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "-- that it was a good movie.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "that", "it", "was", "a", "good", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "When did you watch it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "watch", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Three years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Three", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "You first saw \"The Sting\" three years ago?", "question_tokens": ["You", "first", "saw", "``", "The", "Sting", "''", "three", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I saw it with my family three years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "it", "with", "my", "family", "three", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What did you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "For my mind -- it was a good movie.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "my", "mind", "--", "it", "was", "a", "good", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Butch Cassidy"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "``", "VB", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Have you seen \"Butch Cassidy\"?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "``", "Butch", "Cassidy", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I did see \"Butch Cassidy.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "see", "``", "Butch", "Cassidy", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Butch Cassidy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Ready?", "question_tokens": ["Ready", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "No, we'll jump.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "'ll", "jump", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 150, "question": "-- what goes through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "When I --", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "When you watch these films decades later?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watch", "these", "films", "decades", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, seeing that of course reminds me of my good friend Paul.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "seeing", "that", "of", "course", "reminds", "me", "of", "my", "good", "friend", "Paul", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you have a favorite Redford movie?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "favorite", "Redford", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I think the -- yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "--", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Redford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "How good of a shot are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "of", "a", "shot", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I'm a good shot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "good", "shot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "You (INAUDIBLE) shots?", "question_tokens": ["You", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "shots", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I love -- I love -- I had a gun -- they gave me a gun two weeks before the film and I would strap on a holster and as you walk on, just drawing whenever I could because I want to be able to not have them speed up the camera so it was fun.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "--", "I", "love", "--", "I", "had", "a", "gun", "--", "they", "gave", "me", "a", "gun", "two", "weeks", "before", "the", "film", "and", "I", "would", "strap", "on", "a", "holster", "and", "as", "you", "walk", "on", ",", "just", "drawing", "whenever", "I", "could", "because", "I", "want", "to", "be", "able", "to", "not", "have", "them", "speed", "up", "the", "camera", "so", "it", "was", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "But if you were able to, which -- other than \"Butch Cassidy\" which parts of your film career would you most like people to focus on?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "were", "able", "to", ",", "which", "--", "other", "than", "``", "Butch", "Cassidy", "''", "which", "parts", "of", "your", "film", "career", "would", "you", "most", "like", "people", "to", "focus", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", ",", "WDT", ":", "JJ", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, I've enjoyed a lot of the films that I've made.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "enjoyed", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "films", "that", "I", "'ve", "made", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Butch Cassidy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "\"Ordinary People\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Ordinary", "People", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "\"Ordinary People\" because that was the first directing job.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Ordinary", "People", "''", "because", "that", "was", "the", "first", "directing", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "man", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "He had a very short attention span.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "a", "very", "short", "attention", "span", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "CAVOY: Where is his (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["CAVOY", ":", "Where", "is", "his", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Did you see a parallel between actions taken by the Bush administration, for example, after 9/11, and what you saw in your movie?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "a", "parallel", "between", "actions", "taken", "by", "the", "Bush", "administration", ",", "for", "example", ",", "after", "9/11", ",", "and", "what", "you", "saw", "in", "your", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I don't think it was exclusive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "was", "exclusive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "That it mattered to you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "it", "mattered", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Yes, I think -- it's a twofold.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "twofold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "How was it for you to immerse yourself in the American civil war like this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "was", "it", "for", "you", "to", "immerse", "yourself", "in", "the", "American", "civil", "war", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "It was quite -- I suppose it wasn't that difficult of a thing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "quite", "--", "I", "suppose", "it", "was", "n't", "that", "difficult", "of", "a", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What happens then for a young actor?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "then", "for", "a", "young", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, he's very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Did you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "You feel like you should be calling him Sir Robert, but anyway --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "feel", "like", "you", "should", "be", "calling", "him", "Sir", "Robert", ",", "but", "anyway", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Did you call Robert Redford Bob?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "call", "Robert", "Redford", "Bob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Yes, please rewind it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "please", "rewind", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Redford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Can I just say one thing about James?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "just", "say", "one", "thing", "about", "James", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James", "Robin Wright"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "She didn't need to because I wanted her -- I wanted James and Robin Wright off the bat.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "need", "to", "because", "I", "wanted", "her", "--", "I", "wanted", "James", "and", "Robin", "Wright", "off", "the", "bat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Robin?", "question_tokens": ["Robin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I didn't read the script.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "read", "the", "script", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "You never read the script?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "read", "the", "script", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I read it after I met with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "read", "it", "after", "I", "met", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", ":", "CD", "NNP", "NNP"], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Your power knows -- it just has no bounds, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "power", "knows", "--", "it", "just", "has", "no", "bounds", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "You don't mind if I'm not here for -- (LAUGHTER)", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "mind", "if", "I", "'m", "not", "here", "for", "--", "(", "LAUGHTER", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "I mean do you believe looking what happened in your movie, that what's going on now with Guantanamo is fundamentally wrong, that it's unjust?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "believe", "looking", "what", "happened", "in", "your", "movie", ",", "that", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "now", "with", "Guantanamo", "is", "fundamentally", "wrong", ",", "that", "it", "'s", "unjust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- I mean the parallel is there --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "--", "I", "mean", "the", "parallel", "is", "there", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rumsfeld"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Well, you played a Dick Cheney role, don't you really?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "played", "a", "Dick", "Cheney", "role", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Or Rumsfeld or a combination thereof.", "answer_tokens": ["Or", "Rumsfeld", "or", "a", "combination", "thereof", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Cheney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Bob party?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Bob party.", "answer_tokens": ["Bob", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "And how would you view a country ran by Sarah Palin?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "would", "you", "view", "a", "country", "ran", "by", "Sarah", "Palin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I wouldn't -- I wouldn't even view it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "even", "view", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What's your take on America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "take", "on", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["Awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "And do you admire that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "admire", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "And your question is?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "question", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I don't know what the question is, this is a developing patent that I'm concerned about.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "question", "is", ",", "this", "is", "a", "developing", "patent", "that", "I", "'m", "concerned", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Could you?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "When you see what's going on in Guantanamo Bay, for example, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "Guantanamo", "Bay", ",", "for", "example", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, that's a big question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "big", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo Bay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "and I think that given the premise of your movie, Robert, I mean, do you share that discomfort that your president right now has allowed Guantanamo to continue, when he said that he'd shut it down?", "question_tokens": ["and", "I", "think", "that", "given", "the", "premise", "of", "your", "movie", ",", "Robert", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "share", "that", "discomfort", "that", "your", "president", "right", "now", "has", "allowed", "Guantanamo", "to", "continue", ",", "when", "he", "said", "that", "he", "'d", "shut", "it", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "EDFORD: In terms of the Guantanamo issue, I'm going to now be political and tell you, I don't -- I'm not comfortable because of the film.", "answer_tokens": ["EDFORD", ":", "In", "terms", "of", "the", "Guantanamo", "issue", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "now", "be", "political", "and", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "comfortable", "because", "of", "the", "film", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Robert", "Guantanamo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Was he wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "It's a true story.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "true", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "What do you look for in a great actor or actress?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "look", "for", "in", "a", "great", "actor", "or", "actress", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "It starts with craft.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "starts", "with", "craft", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Where do I sign?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "I", "sign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "It was where do I sign, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "where", "do", "I", "sign", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "When you work with a cast as talented and varied as this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "work", "with", "a", "cast", "as", "talented", "and", "varied", "as", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Oh, wow, I'm just very humbled by everyone sitting at this table right now, and just honored to be a part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "wow", ",", "I", "'m", "just", "very", "humbled", "by", "everyone", "sitting", "at", "this", "table", "right", "now", ",", "and", "just", "honored", "to", "be", "a", "part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Include this part of the table?", "question_tokens": ["Include", "this", "part", "of", "the", "table", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Especially you.", "answer_tokens": ["Especially", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you were young, you would call Robert Redford Bob?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "when", "you", "were", "young", ",", "you", "would", "call", "Robert", "Redford", "Bob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Redford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Have you ever had anything in your life where you had to make a decision of that kind of magnitude?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "anything", "in", "your", "life", "where", "you", "had", "to", "make", "a", "decision", "of", "that", "kind", "of", "magnitude", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Fortunately, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Fortunately", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Not bearding off, but on the humor level, I mean, is he as mischievous as I would hope he'd be on a movie set?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "bearding", "off", ",", "but", "on", "the", "humor", "level", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "is", "he", "as", "mischievous", "as", "I", "would", "hope", "he", "'d", "be", "on", "a", "movie", "set", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "RP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "CAVOY: He is.", "answer_tokens": ["CAVOY", ":", "He", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Was it good fun to make this film?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "good", "fun", "to", "make", "this", "film", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I think I have about 60 new crow's feet thanks to the -- we laughed so much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "have", "about", "60", "new", "crow", "'s", "feet", "thanks", "to", "the", "--", "we", "laughed", "so", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Why am I just finding that out now?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "am", "I", "just", "finding", "that", "out", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Oh, that was the dream man.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "that", "was", "the", "dream", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "What movies have you done, Bob?", "question_tokens": ["What", "movies", "have", "you", "done", ",", "Bob", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Somehow it's gone out of my mind.", "answer_tokens": ["Somehow", "it", "'s", "gone", "out", "of", "my", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "That was you, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "you", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Tom?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "I like al of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "al", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Butch Cassidy"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 760, "question": "Ellen?", "question_tokens": ["Ellen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "Well, I'm going to have to say \"Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "to", "say", "``", "Butch", "Cassidy", "and", "the", "Sundance", "Kid", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "That you wrote?", "question_tokens": ["That", "you", "wrote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "You want to sing it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "sing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Bended knee?", "question_tokens": ["Bended", "knee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "Maybe later.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "You must be ready for one, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "ready", "for", "one", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "Yeah, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Have you got one in the pipeline?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "one", "in", "the", "pipeline", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "-- clues?", "question_tokens": ["--", "clues", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Any co-stars?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "co-stars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 800, "question": "Does she start all the sequel rumors?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "start", "all", "the", "sequel", "rumors", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 801, "answer": "I think she has all the rights.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "has", "all", "the", "rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Evan, what are you up to next?", "question_tokens": ["Evan", ",", "what", "are", "you", "up", "to", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "I actually just finished another political film called \"The Ides of March.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "just", "finished", "another", "political", "film", "called", "``", "The", "Ides", "of", "March", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Clooney or Redford?", "question_tokens": ["Clooney", "or", "Redford", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Oh, don't make me choose.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "do", "n't", "make", "me", "choose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Tom, what are you up to?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", ",", "what", "are", "you", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "Don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Not sure yet?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "sure", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "I'm not sure yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ulysses S. Grant"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 820, "question": "-- quintet?", "question_tokens": ["--", "quintet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 821, "answer": "There is a Ulysses S. Grant role that's coming up, which is quite good.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "Ulysses", "S.", "Grant", "role", "that", "'s", "coming", "up", ",", "which", "is", "quite", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "And isn't there a movie with Judi Dench?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "n't", "there", "a", "movie", "with", "Judi", "Dench", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judi Dench"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "When is that coming out?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "that", "coming", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "Don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lawrence Kasdan", "Diane Keaton", "Diane Wiest"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "Kevin, what are you going to be up to next?", "question_tokens": ["Kevin", ",", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "up", "to", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "I've shot a film that some -- with Lawrence Kasdan directing, with Diane Keaton and Diane Wiest, a wonderful cast.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "shot", "a", "film", "that", "some", "--", "with", "Lawrence", "Kasdan", "directing", ",", "with", "Diane", "Keaton", "and", "Diane", "Wiest", ",", "a", "wonderful", "cast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "Comedy?", "question_tokens": ["Comedy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 845, "question": "Robin, next project?", "question_tokens": ["Robin", ",", "next", "project", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "Still shooting \"Girl With the Dragon Tattoo.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Still", "shooting", "``", "Girl", "With", "the", "Dragon", "Tattoo", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 847, "question": "And any truth you're never going to work with McAvoy again?", "question_tokens": ["And", "any", "truth", "you", "'re", "never", "going", "to", "work", "with", "McAvoy", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 848, "answer": "We thought there would be a sequel to \"the Conspirator.\"", "answer_tokens": ["We", "thought", "there", "would", "be", "a", "sequel", "to", "``", "the", "Conspirator", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McAvoy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "James, what's in the pipeline for you?", "question_tokens": ["James", ",", "what", "'s", "in", "the", "pipeline", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "I'm going to do a film called \"Welcome to the Punch\" in London.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "do", "a", "film", "called", "``", "Welcome", "to", "the", "Punch", "''", "in", "London", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]